in this problem
we've been given a hash and we're asked
to rewrite this car hash as a nested
array
and within this nested array we want
these key value pairs to still be
associated with one another
so we'll call our nested array card and
we'll hold each key value pair
in its own subarray
although we have our key value pairs
grouped together
in subarrays within this outer array
it's going to be a little bit more
difficult for
us to retrieve these values
for example if we want to retrieve the
color from our car
hash we can use element reference
and pass in the key these keys work as
labels for our data
to retrieve the same value from our
nested array
we would need to use both the index of
our subarray
and the index of the string blue
the code on both lines 9 and 10 will
return the same result
however line 9 will be a little bit
easier for
any type of data that has some label
associated with it
typically we would use arrays for
ordered lists
where order matters and we use hashes
where we want to
label our data
so keep in mind the pros and cons of
different types of collections when you
decide
which type of collection to use in your
code